A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3 FA388
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Philippines, 1950-1994; 242; 85 Box(es)
  - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950-1992; 242.D
    Scope and Contents note
    The International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) had a certain elegance. Founded in 1960 as a joint project of the Rockefeller and Ford Foundations, the Institute aimed to tackle the "food production problem" in Asia, with the goal of "closing the gap between the demand for rice and available supplies." The Ford Foundation funded the buildings and equipment, while the RF assumed responsibility for the scientific direction and management. The University of the Philippines (UP) gave IRRI a long-term lease on its site adjoining the College of Agriculture at Los Banos.
    IRRI approached its mission with urgency and exuberance. In December 1963, Sterling Wortman entitled his seminar presentation, "Rice Research: A Race against Time." Having defined the problem as one of inadequate yields, owing primarily to poor agricultural practices and unimproved varieties, the researchers and staff of IRRI set out to revolutionize rice production in Asia. Bolstered by its crop improvement programs in Mexico and India, the RF brought its science and experience to bear on rice in Asia.
    Construction began in November 1960, and administration, dormitory, library and research buildings were completed for dedication ceremonies in February 1962. From the spring of 1961, IRRI had begun to collect and catalogue a "world rice collection" of seeds and genetic material. It assembled a library of rice publications and prepared an international bibliography on rice. By early 1962, irrigated fields awaited experimental planting, and research and training programs soon started up in conjunction with the College of Agriculture.
    In the early years, especially, the RF recruited many of its own agricultural staff veterans to fill research positions at IRRI. The goal, however, was to make IRRI an Asian research institute. IRRI sought a representative distribution of Asian nations on its governing board, and it hoped, through fellowships and the training and research opportunities it afforded, to supply the skilled rice specialists needed to continue the mission both at IRRI and back in their home countries.
    IRRI's "elegance" seemed to some also a liability. In making IRRI a world-class facility, there was concern that the "luxury" of IRRI's laboratories and residences would engender resentment from the neighboring College of Agriculture. But its sponsors meant IRRI to be a model and a beacon, the quality of its facilities reflecting the nobility of its aspirations and the seriousness of its purpose.
    A heady enthusiasm characterized the early reports of IRRI's research. Plant breeders worked to develop rice varieties that were "short, stiff-strawed, early maturing, disease-resistant, and non-sensitive to time of day." These varieties would both produce more grain and be less likely to lodge or buckle, reducing grain losses in the field. Early maturation meant that one could harvest two crops a year. Agronomists, chemists, engineers - and communication specialists - worked alongside the breeders, testing fertilizers, pesticides, and nutritional components, designing multiple-cropping schemes, and devising floating tractors and electric rat fences.
    In late 1966, IRRI named its first major rice variety, IR 8, soon known as "Miracle Rice." IRRI already drew a steady stream of visitors and had inspired several magazine articles, but Miracle Rice was a sensation. President Marcos sent the Shah of Iran a packet of IR 8 seeds as his coronation gift and at home launched his own government-sponsored production campaign. IRRI distributed seeds (and "Do-It-Yourself-Rice Kits") to governments and agricultural stations throughout "free" Asia. There was some speculation that Miracle Rice would win the Cold War.
    Other varieties followed, and the impact on rice production was dramatic. Whereas top yields in 1962 had been around 4.5 tons/hectare, in 1968 yields regularly measured seven to ten tons/hectare. In late 1967 it seemed that the Republic of the Philippines was on its way to rice self-sufficiency.
    The production figures did not translate so smoothly from experimental plot to farmers' fields, however. High yields came as part of a "complete package" of improved practices, requiring not just new varieties, but large amounts of fertilizer, proper planting and irrigation, and disease and pest control. Adopted piecemeal, Miracle Rice lost some of its wonder. The package did not always suit local conditions. IRRI developed it varieties in irrigated fields, but most Filipino rice grew not in paddies, but in rain-fed or upland fields. To purchase fertilizer, the small farmer needed access to credit. Electric fences shorted out in irrigated fields. Some found the new rice unpalatable. Agricultural practices could not be taken singly, but involved issues of labor and local environment. Periodic allegations that IRRI was importing diseased stock or engaged in high-risk research also raised spectral subsistence anxieties.
    Increasingly, IRRI realized it needed to "probe in the farmer's world" and study his problems, if it was to understand the lag in rice production. In 1964, IRRI social scientists studied ways to introduce change, and IRRI programs targeted extension workers. The communications office released a film on rice improvement aimed at extension agents and the general public. There was a sense that farmers would eagerly adopt the new technology, if they were properly educated. Extension workers themselves seemed to be an obstacle, so training programs focused on "changing the change agent." The extensive files on Farmer Training document many of IRRI's efforts to match its improvements to the local ground of the small farmer. IRRI also engaged anthropologists, such as Grace Goodell, as interlocutors between the barrios and the laboratory, reverse extension agents who would interpret the farmers to the scientists.
    The records in this series span a period of change and political turmoil in the Philippines. The RF's transition in the early 1970s from University Development to Education for Development coincided with and ostensibly shared some goals with Marcos's New Society, even as the RF and IRRI tried to steer an apolitical and international course. The history of rice improvement is also a history of development efforts in Southeast Asia. In addition to correspondence, the IRRI files contain regular retrospective reports and evaluations of its programs and their successes or failures.
    - Central Luzon State University - Tilapia, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - Central Luzon State University - Tilapia, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - Magsaysay Award Foundation - Food Workshop, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - Magsaysay Award Foundation - Food Workshop - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - Rice - Minutes, 1958-1970 (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - Rice - Minutes, 1971-1983 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - Rice - Front of File Material, 1972-1987 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - Rice, 1950, 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - Rice, January-May 1959 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - Rice, June-September 1959 (Box 16, Folder 154)
    - Rice, October 1959 (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - Rice, November 1959 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    - Rice, December 1959 (Box 16, Folder 157)
    - Rice, January-February 1960 (Box 16, Folder 158)
    - Rice, March 1960 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - Rice, April 1960 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - Rice, May-June 1960 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - Rice, July-December 1960 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - Rice, January-July 1961 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - Rice, August-December 1961 (Box 17, Folder 164)
    - Rice, January 1962 (Box 17, Folder 165)
    - Rice, February 1962 (Box 17, Folder 166)
    - Rice, March-May 1962 (Box 17, Folder 167)
    - Rice, June-December 1962 (Box 17, Folder 168)
    - Rice, January 1963 (Box 17, Folder 169)
    - Rice, February-July 1963 (Box 17, Folder 170)
    - Rice, August-October 1963 (Box 17, Folder 171)
    - Rice, November-December 1963 (Box 17, Folder 172)
    - Rice, January-April 1964 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    - Rice, May 1964 (Box 17, Folder 174)
    - Rice, June-August 1964 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - Rice, September-December 1964 (Box 18, Folder 176)
    - Rice, January-March 1965 (Box 18, Folder 177)
    - Rice, April 1965 (Box 18, Folder 178)
    - Rice, May 1965 (Box 18, Folder 179)
    - Rice, June-December 1965 (Box 18, Folder 180)
    - Rice, January-May 1966 (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - Rice, June-October 1966 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - Rice, November-December 1966 (Box 18, Folder 183)
    - Rice, January-May 1967 (Box 18, Folder 184)
    - Rice, June-September 1967 (Box 18, Folder 185)
    - Rice, October-November 1967 (Box 18, Folder 186)
    - Rice, December 1967 (Box 19, Folder 187)
    - Rice, January-February 1968 (Box 19, Folder 188)
    - Rice, March-June 1968 (Box 19, Folder 189)
    - Rice, July-December 1968 (Box 19, Folder 190)
    - Rice, January-March 1969 (Box 19, Folder 191)
    - Rice, April-May 1969 (Box 19, Folder 192)
    - Rice, June-August 1969 (Box 19, Folder 193)
    - Rice, September-December 1969 (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - Rice, January-June 1970 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - Rice, July-December 1970 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - Rice, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - Rice, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - Rice, January-July 1973 (Box 20, Folder 199)
    - Rice, August-December 1973 (Box 20, Folder 200)
    - Rice, January-June 1974 (Box 20, Folder 201)
    - Rice, August-December 1974 (Box 20, Folder 202)
    - Rice, January-July 1975 (Box 20, Folder 203)
    - Rice, August-December 1975 (Box 20, Folder 204)
    - Rice, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 205)
    - Rice, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 206)
    - Rice, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 207)
    - Rice, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 208)
    - Rice, January-September 1982 (Box 20, Folder 209)
    - Rice, October-December 1982 (Box 21, Folder 210)
    - Rice, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - Rice, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 212)
    - Rice, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 213)
    - Rice, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 214)
    - Rice, January-August 1987 (Box 21, Folder 215)
    - Rice, September 1987 (Box 21, Folder 216)
    - Rice, October-December 1987 (Box 21, Folder 217)
    - Rice, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 218)
    - Rice, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 219)
      Time sensitive material - Open in 2013.
    - Rice - Supplementary Material (I), 1962, 1964, 1967; Folder 1 of 6 (Box 22, Folder 220)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material (II), 1969; Folder 2 of 6 (Box 22, Folder 221)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material (III), 1971-1972; Folder 3 of 6 (Box 22, Folder 222)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material (IV), 1972-1973; Folder 4 of 6 (Box 22, Folder 223)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material (V), 1982; Folder 5 of 6 (Box 22, Folder 224)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material (VI), 1982-1983; Folder 6 of 6 (Box 22, Folder 225)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (I), 1964; Folder 1 of 11 (Box 22, Folder 226)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (II), 1965; Folder 2 of 11 (Box 22, Folder 227)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (III), 1967; Folder 3 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (IV), 1968; Folder 4 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (V), 1969; Folder 5 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (VI), 1970; Folder 6 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (VII), 1971; Folder 7 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (VIII), 1972; Folder 8 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (IX), 1974; Folder 9 of 11 (Box 23, Folder 234)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (X), 1976; Folder 10 of 11 (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Board Meetings (XI), 1976; Folder 11 of 11 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Bulletins (I), August 1964; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Bulletins (II), October 1964-1965; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Bulletins (III), 1966; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 24, Folder 239)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Bulletins (IV), [1966]; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 24, Folder 240)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - International Rice Testing Program Reports, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 241)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Research Program Review (I), 1968; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 242)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Research Program Review (II), 1968; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 243)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Research Program Review (III), 1968; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Research Program Review (IV), 1968; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Seminar on Field Experimentation with Rice (I), 1968; Folder 1 of 5 (Box 25, Folder 246)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Seminar on Field Experimentation with Rice (II), 1968; Folder 2 of 5 (Box 25, Folder 247)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Seminar on Field Experimentation with Rice (III), 1968; Folder 3 of 5 (Box 25, Folder 248)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Seminar on Field Experimentation with Rice (IV), 1968; Folder 4 of 5 (Box 25, Folder 249)
    - Rice - Supplementary Material - Seminar on Field Experimentation with Rice (V), 1968; Folder 5 of 5 (Box 25, Folder 250)
    - Rice - Administration, June-September 1959 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - Rice - Administration, October 1959 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Rice - Administration, November-December 1959 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Rice - Administration, January-February 1960 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - Rice - Administration, March 1960 (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - Rice - Administration, April 1960 (Box 26, Folder 256)
    - Rice - Administration, May 1960 (Box 26, Folder 257)
    - Rice - Administration, June-July 1960 (Box 26, Folder 258)
    - Rice - Administration, August 1960 (Box 26, Folder 259)
    - Rice - Administration, September 1960 (Box 26, Folder 260)
    - Rice - Administration, October-November 1960 (Box 26, Folder 261)
    - Rice - Administration, December 1960 (Box 26, Folder 262)
    - Rice - Administration, January-February 1961 (Box 27, Folder 263)
    - Rice - Administration, March-April 1961 (Box 27, Folder 264)
    - Rice - Administration, May-June 1961 (Box 27, Folder 265)
    - Rice - Administration, July-August 1961 (Box 27, Folder 266)
      See also Box 85, Folder 2.
    - Rice - Administration, September-October 1961 (Box 27, Folder 267)
    - Rice - Administration, November-December 1961 (Box 27, Folder 268)
    - Rice - Administration, January-March 1962 (Box 27, Folder 269)
    - Rice - Administration, April-May 1962 (Box 27, Folder 270)
    - Rice - Administration, June-September 1962 (Box 27, Folder 271)
    - Rice - Administration, October-December 1962 (Box 27, Folder 272)
    - Rice - Administration, January-March 1963 (Box 27, Folder 273)
    - Rice - Administration, April-July 1963 (Box 28, Folder 274)
    - Rice - Administration, August-September 1963 (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - Rice - Administration, October-December 1963 (Box 28, Folder 276)
    - Rice - Administration, January-March 1964 (Box 28, Folder 277)
    - Rice - Administration, April-August 1964 (Box 28, Folder 278)
    - Rice - Administration, September-October 1964 (Box 28, Folder 279)
    - Rice - Administration, November-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 280)
    - Rice - Administration, January-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 281)
    - Rice - Administration, October-December 1965 (Box 28, Folder 282)
    - Rice - Administration, January-April 1966 (Box 28, Folder 283)
    - Rice - Administration, May-July 1966 (Box 28, Folder 284)
    - Rice - Administration, August-December 1966 (Box 28, Folder 285)
      See also Box 85, Folder 3.
    - Rice - Administration, January-May 1967 (Box 29, Folder 286)
    - Rice - Administration, June-August 1967 (Box 29, Folder 287)
    - Rice - Administration, September-December 1967 (Box 29, Folder 288)
      See also Box 85, Folder 4.
    - Rice - Administration, January-June 1968 (Box 29, Folder 289)
    - Rice - Administration, July-December 1968 (Box 29, Folder 290)
      See also Box 85, Folder 5.
    - Rice - Administration, January-September 1969 (Box 29, Folder 291)
    - Rice - Administration, October-December 1969 (Box 29, Folder 292)
    - Rice - Administration, January-April 1970 (Box 29, Folder 293)
    - Rice - Administration, May-July 1970 (Box 29, Folder 294)
    - Rice - Administration, August-October 1970 (Box 29, Folder 295)
    - Rice - Administration, November-December 1970 (Box 29, Folder 296)
    - Rice - Administration, January-March 1971 (Box 29, Folder 297)
    - Rice - Administration, April-September 1971 (Box 30, Folder 298)
    - Rice - Administration, October-November 1971 (Box 30, Folder 299)
    - Rice - Administration, December 1971 (Box 30, Folder 300)
    - Rice - Administration, January 1972 (Box 30, Folder 301)
    - Rice - Administration, February-March 1972 (Box 30, Folder 302)
    - Rice - Administration, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 303)
    - Rice - Administration, May-June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 304)
    - Rice - Administration, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 305)
    - Rice - Administration, August-October 1972 (Box 30, Folder 306)
    - Rice - Administration, November-December 1972 (Box 30, Folder 307)
    - Rice - Administration, January-July 1973 (Box 30, Folder 308)
    - Rice - Administration, August-November 1973 (Box 30, Folder 309)
    - Rice - Administration, December 1973 (Box 31, Folder 310)
    - Rice - Administration, January-April 1974 (Box 31, Folder 311)
    - Rice - Administration, May-June 1974 (Box 31, Folder 312)
    - Rice - Administration, July-September 1974 (Box 31, Folder 313)
    - Rice - Administration, October-November 1974 (Box 31, Folder 314)
    - Rice - Administration, December 1974 (Box 31, Folder 315)
    - Rice - Administration, January-May 1975 (Box 31, Folder 316)
    - Rice - Administration, June-October 1975 (Box 31, Folder 317)
    - Rice - Administration, November-December 1975 (Box 31, Folder 318)
    - Rice - Administration, January-March 1976 (Box 32, Folder 319)
    - Rice - Administration, April-June 1976 (Box 32, Folder 320)
    - Rice - Administration, July-December 1976 (Box 32, Folder 321)
    - Rice - Administration, January-August 1977 (Box 32, Folder 322)
    - Rice - Administration, September-December 1977 (Box 32, Folder 323)
    - Rice - Administration, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 324)
    - Rice - Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 325)
    - Rice - Administration, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 326)
    - Rice - Administration - Central Files, 1974-1975, 1977, 1979, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 327)
    - Rice - Breeding Manual (I), 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 328)
    - Rice - Breeding Manual (II), 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 329)
    - Rice - Breeding Manual - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 330)
    - Rice - Breeding Symposium, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 331)
    - Rice - Chemrawn Conference, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 332)
    - Rice - Chemrawn Conference, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 333)
    - Rice - Chemrawn Conference, 1981-1985 (Box 33, Folder 334)
    - Rice - Chemrawn Conference - Supplementary Material, 1978, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 335)
    - Rice - Chinese Rice Scientists, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 336)
    - Rice - Chinese Translation, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 337)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (I), 1971-1976, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 338)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), 1971 (Box 33, Folder 339)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), 1972 (Box 33, Folder 340)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), January-July 1973 (Box 33, Folder 341)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), August-December 1973 (Box 33, Folder 342)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), January-February 1974 (Box 34, Folder 343)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), March-May 1974 (Box 34, Folder 344)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), June-July 1974 (Box 34, Folder 345)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), August-December 1974 (Box 34, Folder 346)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 347)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), 1977 (Box 34, Folder 348)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 349)
    - Rice - Farmer Training (II), 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 350)
      See also Box 85, Folder 6.
    - Rice - Farmer Training - Evaluation, 1973-1974, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 351)
    - Rice - Farmer Training - Supplementary Material (I), 1971; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 352)
    - Rice - Farmer Training - Supplementary Material (II), 1971; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 353)
    - Rice - Farmer Training - Supplementary Material (III), [1977]; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 354)
    - Rice - Food Production Workshop, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 355)
    - Rice - Food Production Workshop, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 356)
    - Rice - Food Production Workshop - Supplementary Material (I), 1981; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 357)
    - Rice - Food Production Workshop - Supplementary Material (II), 1981-1982; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 358)
    - Rice - Genetics, March-June 1976 (Box 35, Folder 359)
    - Rice - Genetics, July 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 360)
    - Rice - Genetics - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 361)
    - Rice - Genetics - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 362)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E. - Front of File Material, 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 363)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., January-February 1977 (Box 35, Folder 364)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., March-May 1977 (Box 35, Folder 365)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., June-December 1977 (Box 36, Folder 366)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 367)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., January-June 1979 (Box 36, Folder 368)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., July-November 1979 (Box 36, Folder 369)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., January-May 1980 (Box 36, Folder 370)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., June-November 1980 (Box 36, Folder 371)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., January-February 1981 (Box 36, Folder 372)
    - Rice - Goodell, Grace E., March 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 373)
    - Rice - Hybrids, 1968-1969, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 374)
    - Rice - Indian Training, 1969-1972 (Box 36, Folder 375)
    - Rice - Indian Training, 1973-1976 (Box 36, Folder 376)
    - Rice - Indian Training - Evaluation (Box 36, Folder 377)
    - Rice - International Rice Genetics Symposium, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 378)
    - Rice - Nitrogen Fixation, 1975, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 379)
    - Rice - Nutrition, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 380)
    - Rice - Nutrition - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 381)
    - Rice - Paulsen, Gary M., 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 382)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, 1960, 1962, 1965-1968 (Box 37, Folder 383)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, January-July 1968 (Box 37, Folder 384)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, August-December 1968 (Box 37, Folder 385)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, March-October 1969 (Box 37, Folder 386)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, November-December 1969 (Box 37, Folder 387)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, 1970, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 388)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 389)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 390)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 391)
    - Rice - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material (I), 1974-1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 37, Folder 392)